<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>ArtemCodes</title><link>https://artem.codes/</link><description>Hi there! My name is Artem, Let's build something amazing together!</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 22:40:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://artem.codes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to integrate Golang Service with Chat GPT API</title><link>https://artem.codes/posts/golang-server-with-chat-gpt-api/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 22:40:00 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://artem.codes/posts/golang-server-with-chat-gpt-api/</guid><description>How to integrate Golang Service with Chat GPT API. Intro In this tutorial we&amp;rsquo;re going to create a Golang service that communicates with Chat GPT API. The source code you can find https://github.com/bukhavtsov/golang-server-with-chat-gpt-api. As a result you should be able to understand how to do it and change the logic for implementing your own use cases.
Considerations For implementing the solution we need to have:
API Key to Chat GPT API and at the moment Chat GPT doesn&amp;rsquo;t provide free trial, so you&amp;rsquo;ll have to setup your Open API account and pay https://openai.</description></item><item><title>The Incredible Two Pointers technique</title><link>https://artem.codes/posts/two-pointers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 22:40:00 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://artem.codes/posts/two-pointers/</guid><description>Hey there, fellow learners! I&amp;rsquo;m Artem, and today&amp;rsquo;s lesson is all about the incredible Two Pointers technique.
What is the benefit of two pointers technique? Before we start digging into this technique, I want to tell you about the benefit. Two pointers technique can dramatically improve the performance of your solution. It allows you to move from O(n^2), O(n log n) time complexity to O(n)
What is two pointers technique? To understand two pointers technique you should be familiar with the data structures like arrays and linked lists, and master Big O notation.</description></item><item><title>Big O Notation Notes</title><link>https://artem.codes/posts/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 22:40:00 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://artem.codes/posts/my-first-post/</guid><description>Hello everybody and welcome back. My name is Artem and in this blog post we&amp;rsquo;re going to understand what does Big O notation mean and consider the time complexity. So, Let&amp;rsquo;s get to it!
Why it&amp;rsquo;s essential to understand and master Big O? First, it allows you to determine the most efficient solution for task that you need to resolve. Secondly, it potentially could help you to optimise an existing solution that you have implemented already.</description></item></channel></rss>